



Determination

Set Up Objectives

Decision Making

Public Speaking





Making Mobile Applications Based Database



Microsoft Office 2013



Mikrotik Certification
(MTCNA)





Indonesia



English



- Jl. Kauman, Ngabar Kraton, Pasuruan
- github.com/bud1purwanto budi.purwanto15@gmail.com
- **B**udi Purwanto
- 085233233770

CURRICULUM VITAE

BUDI PURWANTO, S.Tr.Kom

Informatics Engineering of State Polytechnic of Malang



Self Description

I am able to work under pressure, work in a team or individually, I really like working with many people and also able to handle many people when they have problems regarding office work matters or not. And lastly, I care about the people I work with. I think I have adequate education and work experience. Besides, I'm always enthusiastic about what I do. This will make a positive contribution to the company's growth.



PERSONAL INFO

Name : Budi Purwanto

Place of Birth : Pasuruan

Date of Birth : January 16, 1997

Gender : **Male** Religion : **Islam**



EDUCATION

2015-2019 Politeknik Negeri Malang

D4-Teknik Informatika IPK 3.64



EXPERIENCE

Work Experience PT. Trias Sentosa, Tbk.

2019 - Present SAP ABAP Developer SQL Developer Organization Experience Lembaga Pers Mahasiswa Kompen

2017-2018 Member



SKILL & EXPERTISE

Design
Video Editing
MS. Word
MS. Excel
Powerpoint

SAP ABAP I

PHP
JavaScript
Java Mobile